{
  "title": "Hiragana Vocabulary Quiz II",
  "description": "Embark on a quiz to test your knowledge of Japanese words. Match the Japanese term with its romanji equivalent.",
    "items": [
      {
        "question": "りんご",
        "answer": "ringo",
        "hint": "The Japanese word for apple.",
        "options": ["kippu", "mizu", "ringo", "haha"]
      },
      {
        "question": "ひと",
        "answer": "hito",
        "hint": "The Japanese word for person.",
        "options": ["haha", "ringo", "hito", "ame"]
      },
      {
        "question": "くるま",
        "answer": "kuruma",
        "hint": "The Japanese word for car.",
        "options": ["kuruma", "yama", "tegami", "kippu"]
      },
      {
        "question": "みず",
        "answer": "mizu",
        "hint": "The Japanese word for water.",
        "options": ["ame", "hito", "mizu", "yama"]
      },
      {
        "question": "きっぷ",
        "answer": "kippu",
        "hint": "The Japanese word for ticket.",
        "options": ["haha", "kippu", "hito", "ringo"]
      },
      {
        "question": "ほん",
        "answer": "hon",
        "hint": "The Japanese word for book.",
        "options": ["yama", "ringo", "tegami", "hon"]
      },
      {
        "question": "てがみ",
        "answer": "tegami",
        "hint": "The Japanese word for letter or mail.",
        "options": ["haha", "tegami", "mizu", "kuruma"]
      },
      {
        "question": "あめ",
        "answer": "ame",
        "hint": "The Japanese word for rain.",
        "options": ["ame", "kippu", "tegami", "kuruma"]
      },
      {
        "question": "はは",
        "answer": "haha",
        "hint": "The Japanese word for mother.",
        "options": ["haha", "ringo", "yama", "kippu"]
      },
      {
        "question": "やま",
        "answer": "yama",
        "hint": "The Japanese word for mountain.",
        "options": ["kippu", "tegami", "yama", "ame"]
      }
    ]
  }
  